redrivervalleyfair.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy – Red River Valley Fair

## PRIVACY POLICY

The Red River Valley Fair Association respects the privacy of every individual who visits our web sites or responds to our e-mail campaigns. This Privacy Policy outlines the type of information we typically collect from our web sites, online advertisements at other web sites and e-mail campaigns, and how we may use that information. This Policy will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want to share personal information with us.  We may update this Policy from time to time, so please check it occasionally.

## THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Red River Valley Fair Association website. On some pages, you can register online, make requests, and register to receive Red River Valley Fair Association information. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information

## THE WAY WE USE INFORMATION

We use the information you provide about yourself when requesting information or entering a competition only to complete that event. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that event.

We use the information you provide about someone else when entering a competition only to confirm that registration. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that registration.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website on our email sign-up page if you would like to receive our email updates. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the Newsletter sign up and click Subscribe.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with sponsors. For example, we may tell a sponsor that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## SUBSCRIPTION SERVICES

News and marketing information, such as information about free ticket giveaways, special ticket promotions or entertainment acts, is sent to you from this site by subscription only. Your e-mail address is the only information we require to fulfill the subscription. We do not share our e-mail database with outside parties. You may unsubscribe at any time using the automated “unsubscribe” feature or by contacting the webmaster at the address listed below.

## LINKS

This site sometimes contains links to other sites. The Red River Valley Fair Association is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We request that third parties with whom we have agreements or relationships follow similar privacy policies. We do not, however, have any responsibility for their actions or policies.

## HOW TO CONTACT US

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at: [info@redrivervalleyfair.com](mailto:info@redrivervalleyfair.com) or see our [Contact Us](https://redrivervalleyfair.com/contact/) page.
